MUSKAN MAHESHWARY

CONTACT

Address: Brampton, Ontario L7A0Z8

Phone: 416-400-9599

Email: muskanmaheshwary@gmail.com

SKILLS

- Project Management
- · Strategic planning and execution
- Customer service
- Performance Monitoring and Evaluation
- · Complex Problem-Solving
- · Data Research and Validation
- Team Leadership
- Process improvements
- · Relationship building
- Quality Assurance

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Resourceful Operations Executive with 4+ years of experience working in domestic and international positions. Hardworking professional leader skilled in both strategic planning and tactical execution. High-achieving with demonstrated skills in integrating operational strategies, building partnerships and developing new revenue streams. Skillfully manage KPIs and internal controls to monitor operational trends and devise forward-thinking solutions. Results-focused, flexible and resilient in resolving issues.

WORK HISTORY

Operations Coordinator, 02/2022 to Current **Unisync Group Limited** - Mississauga, ON

- Validated results and performed quality assurance to assess accuracy of data.
- Provided direction and guidance to internal teams in order to achieve targets.
- Performed system analysis, documentation, testing, implementation and user support for platform transitions.
- Analyzed program data to provide input for key decision making and strategic planning.
- Maximized team knowledge and productivity by training, monitoring and directing employees in application of best practices and regulatory protocols.
- Developed and implemented daily operations plans such as delivery routes, employee assignments and promotional strategies.
- Oversaw day-to-day operations of large teams across several sites.
- Collaborated with area managers to evaluate needs and optimize operational plans.
- · Worked with vendors to make purchases and reconcile invoices.
- Applied performance data to evaluate and improve operations, target current business conditions and forecast needs.
- Implemented troubleshooting, root cause analysis and issue resolution.

Operations Executive, 08/2021 to 02/2022 **Graphy by Unacademy**

- Created and managed knowledge base to offer staff and customers immediate informational access to products, services and organization.
- Defined strategic goals and worked with teams, departments, technology and processes to align systems to targets.
- Assisted with proactive client outreach initiatives through emails and documented client correspondence in Intercom.
- Established and maintained productive working relationships with staff to resolve operational difficulties and to promote interdisciplinary, collaborative approach to customer service provision.
- Efficiently and effectively identified and solved all problems that impacted

direction of business.

 Applied performance data to evaluate and improve operations, target current business conditions and forecast needs.

Operations Executive, 08/2018 to 06/2021 **OYO** - Gurugram, Haryana

- Worked as a Team Leader, managing a team of 3 people, aligning and managing cross functional collaboration.
- Built and strengthened relationships across functional leadership areas to keep revenue development and operational plans interconnected and effective.
- Managed cross-functional collaboration to drive team engagement and keep members on course to achieve demanding company targets.
- Applied excellent problem-solving, process development and strategic implementation skills to lead and support all areas of operations.
- Use performance optimization strategies and efficiency improvements and drive more business.
- Fostered procedural improvements through effective leadership. Defined strategic goals and worked with team.

Marketing Intern, 10/2017 to 02/2018 Poang - Malta

- POANG is a game development company operating from the island of Malta.
- POANG Fantasy Football, is a one of a kind hybrid between traditional season-long fantasy football and role-playing football manager games.
- Worked as a web marketer for the company help them market the recently launched gaming app designed editorial content strategy curated and segment editorial content to increase engagement and growth increased average weekly Facebook reach.

EDUCATION

 $\begin{tabular}{ll} \textbf{Master of Business Administration}: Business Administration, 2018 \\ \textbf{Thapar University} - Chandigarh \\ \end{tabular}$

2013

Jaypee University of Information AndTechnology - Solan, Himachal Pradesh

SOFTWARE

- SPSS
- SQL
- Microsoft Excel

LANGUAGES

- English
- Hindi
- Punjabi
- French